Sometimes I remember
when it wasn't like this.
- Don't do that.
- Do what?
[Tabitha] Why is there a tree
in the middle of the road?
- [crows cawing]
- How is this possible?
We're on the same fucking road.
- [tires squeal]
- [horn blares]
Oh, my God!
[Donna] There are things
you need to know
about where you are,
about the way things are now.
- Do you believe in monsters?
- Meagan, no!
We have an arrangement,
sheriff.
You don't come here.
I came to see my son,
Donna.
We lost a couple of people
last night.
Look, I'm a little busy,
so if that's all...
That's all.
I built a software company based
on nothing but imagination,
but this?
It was here and then it wasn't.
- [shrieks]
- [screams]
There was this weird fucking
symbol right on the ceiling.
What are you
looking for, hmm?
I think there's two pages
stuck together here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[speaks Cantonese]
You're from
one of those two cars?
- What do you think it means?
- Please don't.
Victor,
take your peaches and shoo.
He's creepy,
but he's harmless.
He's just been here
a really long time.
[dog barks]
[Ethan] What is that?
A faraway Tree. Watch.
It works for people, too.
- Really?
- Problem is,
you never know
where you'll end up.
When Thomas died,
something inside of me broke.
So we pretended
everything was fine,
and I think that just made
everything worse.
Sorry.
[Jim]
I just feel so broken.
We're gonna figure it out
together.
- Don't worry.
- [Sara panting]
I hear their voices.
They told me
this was the last one
- Mom!
- then everyone gets to go home.
- Ow!
- Ethan, run!
No! You don't understand.
[flesh slices, blood gurgles]
- Nathan, please!
- Nathan.
I wish you had the luxury
of grief, but you don't, Boyd.
These people need you.
You need to be the one
to lead these people home.
[Boyd] No!
- [wheezing]
- Stay with me.
[Abby] The only way for us
to go home
is to wake everyone up.
- Abby, stop.
- [Fatima] What happened...
- Mom!
- ...wasn't your dad's fault.
- No, no!
- [gunshot]
And it wasn't yours.
It was this place.
- [Ellis] Dad, I'm so sorry.
- No, no. Hey. Hey, no.
This is not goodbye.
What is she doing here?
She might be helpful
for us to find out
what we're
looking for out there.
No one can know she's with me.
Where are we going?
To find our way home.
How about you and I
have an adventure?
The game's gonna be called
"Where does the light
come from?"
[Kenny] You don't think
the tower's gonna work?
[Donna] You guys look
at Colony House
and figure it's all just
drinking and fucking.
It was more than that.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
[Donna] There was joy
in that house.
If it does work,
I think you'll find
there's more you're gonna miss
about this place
than you thought.
[Kristi] Iceland. Nice.
If this radio thing works,
maybe we could go.
I'm engaged.
Part of me really wants
to go back
and find out the woman I fell
in love with waited for me.
What does the other part want?
To go to Iceland with
the most amazing guy I met.
[Ellis]
You are the love of my life.
We could be anywhere
in the world,
but it would not matter
because you are my home.
- [static]
- [Jim] It's working.
We got a signal!
- Where are you?
- [man] Is this Jim?
Your wife shouldn't be
digging that hole, Jim.
[shouts]
[electricity zapping]
What the fuck?
You're here.
We have to go.
- This is where they sleep.
- Oh, my God.
Tabitha!
[Boy in white] It's angry now.
You have to get inside.
You'll be safe in there.
I'll follow behind.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
["A Hard Rain's A-Gonna Fall"
plays]
♪ Oh, where have you been
My blue-eyed son♪
[bell ringing]
♪ And where have you been
My darling young one♪
♪ I've stumbled on the side
Of 12 misty mountains♪
♪ I've walked and I crawled
On six crooked highways♪
♪ And I've stepped in the middle
Of seven sad forests♪
♪ I've been out in front of
A dozen dead oceans♪
[thunder rumbles]
♪ I been 10,000 miles
In the mouth of a graveyard♪
♪ And it's a hard
It's a hard♪
♪ It's a hard, it's a hard♪
[bell ringing]
♪ It's a hard rain's♪
♪ A-gonna fall♪
[gasps, pants]
[grunts]
Okay. Okay.
[grunting]
[grunts]
Hello?
Oh. Okay. All right.
Okay.
[pants]
[grunts]
[shouts]
Motherfuckin' fuck you!
Fuckin'--fuck!
[music plays through earbuds]
♪ And what did you hear
My blue-eyed son♪
My darling young one♪
No, no, no, no, no.
Jesus.
What the fuck?
- Stop the bus!
- What?
Hey, bro. It's fine.
We just took a little detour.
[man] No.
We have to turn around.
- We can't be here.
- [woman] Sit down.
- [man] Please! Please!
- Hey. It's alright, man.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- We have to--
Go sit the fuck down, okay?
Can you please
just stop the bus?
Everyone please return
to your seats!
- Come on. That's it.
- You don't understand.
Bad things
are gonna happen if--
- [vomits]
- [others exclaim in revulsion]
- Oh, God.
- Jesus. Stop the goddamn bus!
♪ It's a hard, it's a hard♪
♪ It's a hard rain's♪
♪ A-gonna fall♪
["Que Sera, Sera [Whatever
Will Be, Will Be]" plays]
♪ When I was just
A little boy♪
♪ I asked my father♪
♪ "What will I be?"♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?"♪
♪ "Will I be rich?"♪
♪ Here's what he said to me♪
♪ Que sera sera♪
♪ Whatever will be will be♪
♪ The future's
Not ours to see♪
♪ Que sera sera♪
♪ What will be
Will be ♪
♪ Now I have
Children of my own♪
♪ They ask their father♪
♪ "What will I be?"♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?"♪
♪ "Will I be rich?"♪
♪ I tell them tenderly♪
♪ Que sera sera♪
♪ Whatever will be will be♪
♪ The future's not ours to see♪
♪ Que sera sera♪
♪ What will be will be♪
- Cover the circuit boards!
- Just keep it steady.
[Jade] Stuff's getting
destroyed. Grab everything!
- [shouts]
- Oh, fuck!
- [Donna] Get back.
- Pull them back.
Stay away from
the lights!
Kristi,
we need you in here.
- [Kristi] Coming.
- Check the windows.
Lock this place down.
- Okay. Let me see.
- Ah, God.
There's something in my eye.
- Yep. Stay with me.
- Ow!
- Got it?
- Give me that pole there.
Wait, wait, wait.
[Jade]
Get someone on the roof.
We need that goddamn winch
tied down.
That looks like a car radio.
These, guys. These speakers.
Grab the speakers.
Get everything inside.
Fuck!
[man 1] One more piece of that.
Hold on.
See if you can tie it down.
[man 2] With what?
There's nothing up here.
Fuck me.
Donna, why did my dad
run off like that?
- Julie, please.
- [Ellis] I'm on it.
Donna! Donna!
We have a problem.
- [Donna] Get the kids upstairs.
- What?
- Ethan? Hey, hey.
- [Ellis] Get them upstairs.
- [Jade] Donna!
- How about you and I
go upstairs, huh?
[screaming]
Ellis, go get her!
Bring her back here!
I got it.
- Donna?!
- Don't touch it.
We're gonna take you in the
kitchen and clean you up, okay?
- Donna?
- [Donna] Check the windows
and lock this place down.
- Donna!!
- What?
There is a bus parked outside
the diner!
Tabitha?
Are you down there?
Shit.
Tabitha?
Come on, baby. Please.
[Tabitha inhaling and exhaling]
Come.
- Where are we going?
- [quietly] Shh! We can't talk.
They're close now.
You'll wake them.
- Wake who?
- Shh!
No, no, no.
Victor, we need to stop.
You need to tell me
what's going on.
- Where are we?
- We're underneath the town.
This is where the monsters live.
This is where they sleep.
But I can get us out.
The boy in white,
he showed me the way.
The what?
I went through the tree,
then I was here.
He told me to wait for you.
He showed me where to hide.
It's okay to be scared.
We just need to be quiet.
We just have to--
- What the fuck?
- What?
We have to hurry.
They'll be awake soon.
Yeah.
- Deep breath, okay?
- Okay.
Yeah. Don't touch.
All right.
One, two... three.
Aah!
Don't touch it, okay?
You're doing great.
All right. Don't touch.
Don't touch.
Tell everyone
unless they're bleeding,
they better be securing
the goddamn windows.
Okay.
- Mattias, grab the shotguns.
- Got it.
We don't need to do that.
No?
There's a fucking bus
down there.
God knows how many people
with zero idea
of the shit storm
they just rolled into.
How do you think
they're gonna react
when we tell them
they can't leave?
Look.
We have a long night
ahead of us.
Boyd picked one hell of a time
to go on safari.
If this shit goes sideways,
you have to be ready to step up.
You got that?
You're sheriff now.
- Kristi?
- Yeah?
Grab your stuff.
Meet us down at the diner.
We're about to make
some new friends.
[passenger laughing]
It's locked.
[laughs, whoops]
Fuckin' shirt.
You all, come join me!
Ha ha!
Whoo! Whoo!
Ahh.
Oh, the sun! Ha ha ha!
No way.
Ah.
Rain dance is done.
Just follow my finger
with your eyes.
Good.
Great. Okay.
Can I see your hand?
Okay, pulse is good.
No sign of a fever.
Look,
I need everybody off the bus.
Seriously?
Just give us a minute.
Please?
You a doctor or something?
Pediatric nurse.
Oh.
Hey.
Hey, what's your name?
Elgin.
Elgin?
Elgin, do you know
where you are?
Do you?
Why were you screaming
like that?
I had a really bad dream.
Hey. Hey, what the fuck
was that?
- Hey.
- Back off, man.
Why don't you back off?
I'm the one
with fuckin' puke
on my shirt.
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
You're a goddamn freak.
Let's give him
some space, okay?
Excuse me.
You alright, man?
Smells fuckin' terrible
in here.
Asshole.
Hey, cut the guy
a break.
Do you wanna go outside?
Elgin?
How about I just sit here
with you until you're ready?
Okay?
Okay.
[pants]
Oh, my God.
Julie! Hey.
- I need to find my dad.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Ellis!
Pretty crazy, huh?
Maybe the magic tower
summoned them.
You ever see
something like this?
- [Julie] Dad? Dad?
- Nope. These people are fucked.
[Driver] Everybody?
Everybody gather round.
Gather round.
Just want y'all to sit tight.
I'm gonna clean things up in
there and we'll be on our way.
- Hi. Hey.
- Hi.
Uh, listen.
There's gonna be a bunch
of people on their way down.
- Mmm.
- Um...
And they're gonna help
you guys out, alright?
So we'll get
the diner unlocked,
and we'll get you guys
sorted out.
Okay, well, this isn't
a pit stop, okay?
So unless you have a mop,
I'm good. Thanks.
Holy shit.
What happened?
- The floor just--
- [Jim] I don't know.
Where's Mom?
I, uh... Ethan?
Uh, where's Ethan?
[stammers] He's fine.
He's at Colony.
Dad, is she down there?
Julie, listen to me.
I need you to
get help, okay?
Get as many people
as you can.
Julie!
Okay. All right.
Come here. Come here.
[cries]
Now is the time for you
to be strong.
Your mom needs you, okay?
Go and get help.
- Okay.
- Go. Now.
- You sure you're okay?
- Oh, yeah. I'm fine.
- Okay. Just let me know...
- [Julie] Ellis!
...if you need anything.
What's wrong?
- It's my mom. She's trapped.
- Wait, wait. What?
She was digging in the basement.
My dad's inside.
- She needs help. Please.
- Whoa, whoa. Stay with the bus.
- I got this.
- You sure?
You're not gonna do much
with that.
I'm a bartender.
Crowd control's my thing.
Hey, people? We got a little
situation on our hands here.
Listen up.
There's a woman trapped
in the basement
of that house over there.
Her husband's inside.
We could use some help.
Yeah. All right.
Yeah. I'll help.
- I'm going.
- No, no, no. Just stay there.
Hey, no. I need everyone
to stay by the bus.
Well, there's a woman
trapped in there.
Then let emergency services
handle it.
Oh, you're a peach.
Okay. Okay, look.
You guys go.
Listen. There are people
on the way.
They're gonna help
everyone out, okay?
They're gonna get everything
squared up. You're with--
- Hey! Hey, no. Whoa.
- I'm going, too.
They can't focus on your mom if
they're worried about you. Okay?
Okay, come on. You're
needed here. Come with me.
Remember, the most
important thing is--
Keep everybody calm.
I know.
Uh, you talk to the bus driver,
and I'll get everyone inside.
- Let's go.
- Donna.
We've got some problems.
No shit.
Where's the driver?
Folks, sorry about
your inconvenience here.
Let's get you all inside, huh?
Get some tea brewing.
Get you all warmed up.
Sounds like
a good idea.
- Right? Some tea sounds good.
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
Come on in, guys. Please.
Let's go, folks.
Come on.
Sorry again.
[Tom] Jim!
Oh, thank God.
Who are they?
We, uh...
our bus stopped here.
- Your bus?
- Can you hear anything?
- Is she talking?
- No.
I, uh... no.
What the fuck?
What was she doin' down here?
[Jim] Digging to see
where the wires went.
It doesn't matter.
If she was digging
down here,
what the hell caused that?
Please just help me.
Hey, bud, look at me.
Look at me.
We're gonna get your lady
out of there, okay?
[Jim]
Wait, wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Before you lift anything out,
just make sure that it's not
holding up somethin' else.
Last thing we want is
to collapse things further.
[Tom]
Okay. Yeah. We got this.
Let's get this done quickly,
alright?
Yeah.
Come here. Wait, wait, wait.
[Victor whispering]
Come.
Come on.
Are you sure
this is the right way?
Shh.
Oh, no, no, no.
Victor.
No, we have to
keep going.
No, no, no, Victor.
We have to go back.
No way. There's no going back.
We have to go through.
That's what he said.
We go while they sleep.
You have to be brave.
We both have to be brave.
Sara?
Sara, you up there?
You said we'd be safe
inside this tree. [laughing]
Well, this does not feel
very safe to me, Sara.
[man] Hey.
Hello?
Hey, is anybody up there?
[man in the distance]
Are you real?
What?
[man] Are you real?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I'm real.
Are you?
Are you fuckin' real?
[man]
I can help you if you help me.
Okay.
[man] You promise?
Yeah, man.
Anything you want.
Just please,
just get me outta here, man.
[man] You'll have to climb.
What?
No. I...
[shouts] I can't.
I just... tried.
[man] Wait.
[Boyd] Hey. What-- fuck!
What?
[man] You have to hurry.
They'll be back soon.
Okay. All right.
Uh, okay.
[Clara] Hey.
Do you think
we made it angry?
What are you
talking about?
That storm
came out of nowhere,
and the way
the lights exploded,
it's almost like
we made something angry.
What do we do now?
Well...
I got one rolling paper
left...
...so I'm getting stoned.
Okay.
[ominous synthesizer music
plays]
[dummy screams]
[screams]
Okay. Okay.
Here. I found this.
There's a lot
of broken glass.
[speaks Cantonese]
You careful.
Why do you think
they broke?
That was scary.
Very scary.
Do you think the others
will be back soon?
You don't be afraid.
I protect you.
I'm not afraid.
Well, maybe
a little afraid.
Sometimes
a quest can be scary.
And when it gets close
to the end,
that's when
it gets really scary.
I guess we're sleeping here
tonight?
Whatever.
What are you doing
out here?
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Go back inside.
Why?
Because...
You know, I don't know, kid.
Do whatever you want.
You know cigarettes
are bad for you, right?
It's not that kind
of cigarette.
What's wrong with you?
Gee, I don't know.
I mean... [chuckles]
maybe I just spent
the last week thinking
we might actually
get out of this shit box,
only to see our entire plan
come crashing down around us.
Literally.
So? We try again.
Yeah.
We'll get right on that, kid.
Maybe we'll try
something else.
Whenever the Cromenockle
failed, he always found--
What the fuck
is a Cromenockle?
- Oh. Um--
- No. I don't care.
You're friends with Victor,
right?
Do you know which room
is his?
Why?
[Tabitha whispering]
Okay. Shh.
[Victor whispering]
Look. Right here.
[gasps] Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
[shushes]
Please, please, let's go.
[Tabitha]
Oh, my God.
- Victor?
- Shh.
What?
- No, Victor!
- Come on.
Victor, Victor, Victor?
Victor, Victor?
Victor, which way?
[pants] Victor?
[stammers] I don't know.
I got scared.
What?
This isn't the way
that he told me to go.
- [moans]
- What?
No, no, no. Victor, Victor.
- Hey. Listen to me, Victor.
- Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
Look at me. Look at me.
- [moans]
- Yeah.
I know you're scared.
I'm scared, too,
but we have to
fucking move, okay?
Please. Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
We're going to do this
together, okay?
It's okay. Let's go.
Please, Victor.
Come on, Victor.
Please, please, please.
Let's go.
Let's go here.
There's gotta be
something here!
You shouldn't
be doing this.
Victor wouldn't like it.
All right.
Well, I got news for you, kid.
Victor is, uh,
he's probably dead, alright?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
said that.
It's okay,
'cause you're wrong.
He's fine.
Wherever he is,
he's doing his part.
Yeah? His part of what?
The quest.
Sorry, the what?
That's what this is.
It's a quest,
and everyone has
a part to play. Even you.
Why do you care
so much about Victor?
Because...
All right, look.
Between you and me,
alright,
I have been seeing some
very crazy shit lately.
You swear a lot.
Get over here.
The point is,
every time I see something
really weird, I see this.
This symbol.
Okay.
Okay? I didn't draw this,
though. I found this.
Well, Kenny's mom
gave me tea, and then she--
When she-- Anyway, look.
The point is,
this journal is old, alright?
And whoever it belonged to kept
drawing the same weird symbol
that I have been seeing
over and over
and over again.
I've been looking at this,
and then the other night,
I noticed two of the pages
were stuck together.
And in between there,
there's this, uh,
this old Polaroid.
- What's a Polaroid?
- Jesus fuckin' Christ. It's a--
I'm sorry. It's a photo.
It's like a little photograph.
How do you not know
what a Polaroid is? Come on.
Here, look. This.
See this?
What do you see?
He's got the journal.
Yeah.
What else?
That's Victor's lunchbox.
Ah.
Not just Victor's lunchbox.
That's Victor.
- [Ethan] Really?
- Yeah.
And if he was here
back when that guy was here--
He might know
what the symbol means.
Exactly.
And that's why
I'm in his room.
- So, we good?
- Well...
...symbols
are important,
especially on a quest.
Yeah?
But you have to figure out
if they're good symbols
or bad symbols.
Well, what do you mean?
What do you mean,
"bad symbols"?
Sometimes,
they make you do bad things.
You're a creepy little kid.
Okay. One big step.
There you go.
[Donna]
They will rip you to shreds.
Let's just head around
the front, okay?
[Donna]
It goes on and on.
The point is, these things
don't just kill.
Hold on. Stop.
Is this--are you
out of your fucking mind?
Look, I know
this sounds crazy,
and there is not
a single reason in the world
you should trust me.
But if you get those people
back on this bus
and try to drive out of here,
if you're outside
- when the sun goes down--
- Know what? I'm done.
- Excuse me. Excuse me!
- No. Please.
Seriously.
You can't go back
on that bus.
Get out of my way.
I can't do that.
[Jim grunts]
There's something.
There's something, uh...
there's a chamber
or something underneath.
- Let's lift this thing. Ready?
- Yeah. One, two--
[Tom] Oh, whoa!
Elgin, you okay?
Uh, I was just
a little dizzy.
Okay. You wanna go inside?
We'll try and get you
some water.
I can help you.
Nice and slow.
- You okay?
- Ooh. Whoa, whoa.
Are you okay?
Shit. Shit.
- Elgin?
- [grunting]
I need some help
over here!
Places don't just come apart
like this.
- Jim?
- Uh, wait. We're almost there.
[woman] Hey. Help me. Help me.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
- He just started seizing.
- Okay. Easy, easy.
Elgin, I'm gonna put this
under your head.
Aw, fuck!
I need you to help me
roll him on his side.
One, two, three.
He was sick on the bus.
Stay with me, Elgin.
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
You gotta get out of there, man.
Come on, Jim.
This is the beam
that I gotta get out.
[loud crashing]
Hey, you're okay.
Keep breathing.
- There you go. Good.
- [house frame creaks]
Let's go! Let's go.
Let's go!
- Jim!
- I'm not leaving.
[men yelling]
- Dad!
- Julie!
- Julie, no. Be careful. Stop.
- [Kenny] Wait!
- Dad, can you hear me?
[Donna] Jim!
[tinnitus ringing]
- [Julie] Dad?
- [Donna] Jim?
Dad, are you down there?
[Ellis]
If anyone else is down there--
- [Julie] Dad!
- [Donna] Jim?
- Dad! Dad, can you hear me?
- [ringing stops]
- [groans]
- Dad?
[Donna] Jim, can you hear me?
- [structure groans]
- Hello? Dad, Dad?
- [Donna] Jim.
- Dad, just hang on, okay?
Dad, if you can hear us,
just please hang on.
[grunts]
- Dad, are you there?
- Just hang on, okay?
Dad?
Dad, talk to me, please.
- Dad, Dad!
- Julie.
- Julie?
- Dad, can you hear me?
Julie?
- Dad!
- Julie?
[Kenny]
Over there.
- Dad, I'm here.
- [Jim] Julie?
Jim, we're gonna get you out
of there, alright?
Is there anyone else
down there with you?
You guys better hurry.
- Over there.
- Tom!
Dad, it's okay.
Tom, is there anyone
with you?
[Kenny] Hey, hey. Careful.
Careful with that.
The kid with the jacket,
he's not moving.
[Donna] Is he breathing?
I can't tell.
Dad, listen to me, okay?
We're gonna get you out.
- We just, uh--
- Be careful when you get--
[exhales sharply]
I want you to stay
with Donna.
You do whatever she says,
and you do not leave her side.
Dad, Dad,
we're gonna get you out, okay?
Uh, we just--
We need to do something.
- Jim, we're gonna get you out.
- Hey. I got someone!
Who else
is down there with you?
- [Donna] Is he alive?
- I don't know.
- Hey, man, you alright?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he's okay.
- Get him down here.
- I'm coming.
- Easy. Stand up.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Kristi, can you grab him?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Oh, my God.
- I got you. I got you.
- Hold me. Yeah, good.
- I can't see anyone.
- Whoa, whoa!
Watch your step, guys.
Come on.
- Easy, easy.
- Whoa! Whoa!
- You got him? Alright.
- Nice and slow.
- You're good.
- Alright, Kristi.
- Make sure he's okay.
- Okay. You're good.
- Whoa, whoa! Okay sit.
- I wanna sit down.
[gasping]
[Donna] We're gonna get you
outta there, alright?
[wood creaks]
- Any pain when I touch at all?
- No.
- Down your back here? No?
- No, no.
[panting]
[Tabitha] What is this?
[gasps]
- [whimpers]
- It's okay, Victor.
It's okay.
[shrieks, pants]
You shouldn't have
done that.
- Okay.
- We have to go.
Hey, wait.
Where's the water coming from?
They're waking up.
What?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Victor, Victor, Victor.
No, no, no!
There's a tunnel.
Please, follow it
all the way up. Go, go, go!
Go, go, go. Go, go, go!
Look up.
Good. Any blurriness?
Trouble seeing at all? No?
- No.
- [Kristi] You're good?
Okay. Squeeze my hand.
Squeeze. Good.
Are you feeling okay?
How are you feeling?
You guys still good?
- Here's some water.
- Stay with him.
Wait. Where are you going?
I have to--
Gotta get something
from the bus.
- Take it easy.
- [coughs]
Okay.
It's okay now.
What?
♪
[groans]
- [Ellis] Dad?
- [grunts]
Dad?
It's getting dark.
You said we'd take the boat out.
[man] You okay down there?
Yeah.
Great.
[gasping]
[monsters vocalize
in distance]
Go.
Victor, okay. Go, go, go.
Go, go, go. Go, Victor, go!
Victor?
[groans, pants]
[monsters shriek
in the distance]
Victor, Victor?
Victor, which way?
What?
I don't know.
Which way, Victor?
Which way?
We have to--
We have to go.
This way.
[groans, gasps]
Alright, everybody,
back on the bus.
No, there are people trapped
in there.
That's right, and we need
emergency crews here,
and when we get to the next
town, we'll send some help.
Let's go!
Mattias,
keep an eye on her.
- Yeah. Got it.
- Let's try-- Let's try again.
[Ellis] Hey.
Let's clear this piece.
[Donna] Okay.
Let's see if we can pull it.
[Fatima] Yeah.
Slide this over
and give me a hand.
- Good. You got it.
- Watch out.
Aah! Whoa. Wait.
Wait, wait, wait! Stop, stop.
Wait, wait, wait.
Guys, stop.
- [Donna] Hold the work.
- [Kenny] Everyone stop.
[groans]
Don't move anything else.
Everything here is resting
on something else.
If you move anything
too quickly,
all the rest of it
could come down.
Jim, we don't have time
to be delicate.
Yeah. We can't just stop.
In order to get us
all three out safely,
you have to do it slowly,
and you gotta
do it right.
Dad, the sun is about
to go down.
I know.
That's why you're gonna
leave us here.
What? What? No. No, no, no.
We're not doing that.
- Okay? We're not.
- Yes, yes.
If we cover them up,
leave right now,
those things might not know
they're down there.
We have to give them
a talisman or something.
It won't work.
You can't just wear them
around your neck.
They have to be
inside something--
a house, a car.
There's nothing down there.
Listen, Julie.
I survived here
for almost a year
before Boyd found
those talismans.
If these guys stay quiet,
there's a really
good chance that--
- [ignition turns]
- Oh, for fuck's sake!
Fuck. Kenny?
Yeah. Can you please go into
the diner, grab some tarps?
Yeah, okay.
All right.
Everyone on, right now.
- We're leaving. Come on.
- [indistinct chatter]
Hold on!
Turn off that goddamn bus.
You stay away from us.
You're gonna get people killed,
you realize that?
If you want to stay,
you can make arrangements
with emergency services
once they arrive.
There are no
emergency services.
If you're still outside
when the sun goes down,
you and everyone else on this
little death trap are gonna die.
Whoa, whoa. What the hell
is she talking about?
[Donna]
I'm gonna say this once.
None of you are safe here.
Things are gonna get
really fucking scary
when the sun goes down,
and if you're outside,
you are going to die.
If you want more of
an explanation,
then I'm happy to give it to you
when things settle down.
But meanwhile, if you want to
live through the night,
you need to get your ass
back inside that diner.
Everybody on board.
What does she mean,
"Everybody's gonna die"?
Calm down.
Calm down for a second.
- Fuck this!
- Everyone needs to calm down.
Calm down for--
Are we supposed to buy
that shit?
Calm down.
[indistinct chatter]
- I gotta be in--
- You don't understand!
Start the fucking bus.
Start the--
- [safety catch clicks]
- Donna, no!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the fuck?
[shouting over each other]
- Stop!
- Wait!
- Oh, my God.
- Fatima, get back here!
We can't just leave them!
[Fatima] Hey, come back!
- Fatima.
- [Ellis] Fatima!
[fires shot]
- Stop!
- Fatima!
Inside the diner, now!
Get inside. Get inside.
Get inside!
- Julie?
- Dad? Dad, I'm here.
Oh.
I, uh, I heard gunshots?
Yeah. They just--
They needed to get everybody
into the diner.
Julie, there's, uh...
there's a cavern,
or some kind of space,
underneath the basement.
What?
I saw it when we were clearing
the debris.
If your mother made it
down there,
then that means she's okay.
You hear me?
So, if you could just wait
for her to get back,
then you'll be okay.
- We're gonna get you out, Dad.
- I know, sweetie. I know.
You just be strong, okay?
Julie?
Julie, the sun's almost down.
- We have to get inside.
- No.
[Jim] He's right.
The longer you stay out there,
the more chance they realize
we're down here.
- Come on.
- [crying]
[Jim] You've got to go.
It's okay, honey.
[sobs]
[Jim] I love you.
I love you, too.
Come on. Let's go.
[Kenny] You two guys, too.
Come on. You have to trust me.
We have to get inside.
Let's go. Come on. Please?
Let's go.
Inside. Inside!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[pants]
Got it.
[man] You made it.
What the--
[man] I wasn't sure you would.
It's such a long climb.
[man] We don't have much time.
Is that a gun?
Yeah.
Oh.
My eyes, they're not
what they used to be.
It's good
that you have a gun.
That'll make it easy.
Make what easy?
I need you to kill me.
♪